(Howard:)See?
(Howard:)With the grain.
(Penny:)Wow, that is better.
(Howard:)And someday, when you
have varicose veins,
(Howard:)I'll show you how to massage them.
(Raj:)Oh, God, never again.
I assume by "never again,
" you mean never again will you drink
(Leonard:)all of Penny's beer,
then run down to the gas station
(Leonard:)for a couple of 40s,
a box of Slim Jims
and the latest issue of
Bombay Badonkadonks.
(Raj:)I was homesick.
(Howard:)The highlight of the evening
was when you showed us
(Howard:)your Bollywood break
dancing skills.
(humming Indian music)
(Raj:)That's very offensive.
(Howard:)Yeah, we all thought so.
LEONARD: Oh, no.
(Leonard:)What?
It's John and Yoko.
(Howard:)More like Yoko and Yoko.